innovative-sol.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy - Innovative Solutions

##  GDPR Compliance

Innovative Solutions' programs collect, use and process their users' data. Some data, such as username or e-mail address, is provided directly by the users, and some of it is collected by the programs, in order to ensure efficient functionality.

We at Innovative Solutions believe in transparency towards our users and take responsibility when it comes to respecting your privacy. We value the vital role of personal data protection and we give you the assurance that you are guaranteed the following rights:

  * \- Access to your personal data that we possess;
  * \- Personal data portability;
  * \- Decision over the processing of your personal data;
  * \- Correction of your personal data.
  * \- The right to be forgotten.

In order to use Innovative Solutions' programs, you must be 16 years or older.

##  Cookies

What is a cookie? A "cookie" is a small text file that is stored by your web browser on your computer or mobile device.

We use cookies to help identify your computer so we can tailor your user experience, track shopping basket contents and remember where you are in the order process.

You can disable any cookies already stored on your computer, but these may stop our website from functioning properly.

##  Functional Cookies

Innovative Solutions will track the pages you visit via Google Analytics.

##  The following is strictly necessary in the operation of our website. Innovative Solutions will:

Remember that you are logged in and that your session is secure. You need to be logged in to complete an order.
